A Guide to the Sam Legard Photograph Collection, 1958-2007
Thomas Balch Library
Thomas Balch Library
Sam Legard Photograph Collection 1958-2007
Thomas Balch Library
VC 0037
The collection is composed primarily of aerial photographs of Loudoun County. Most of the photographs are in color and measure 5 x 7 inches, though there are other sizes as well. In some cases, the negatives are also included. The photographs concentrate on new construction and areas slated for development and were often used to establish insurance policies and settle claims.
Sam Legard, Leesburg, VA.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Sam Legard, Leesburg, VA.
Alternative Form Available
None
Accruals
2009.0019; 2009.0023; 2009.0026; 2009.0045
Biographical Information
Sam Legard is the son of Samuel Campbell Legard (1898-1981) and Edith Potts Legard (1897-1960). He was born and spent much of his early life in the Hillsboro area of Loudoun County. As a young man Legard worked on his father's farm. He began selling insurance in the 1950s and operated as an independent insurance agent in Leesburg until he retired. His insurance agency, Sam Legard Insurance, still operates. Legard also explored interests in flying and photography. He combined flying and photography with his professional work as an insurance salesman by taking aerial photographs of areas to be insured and damages covered by policies. He was employed at various times by the Town of Leesburg and Loudoun County to photograph areas of development.
Scope and Content
The collection is composed primarily of aerial photographs of Loudoun County. Most of the photographs are in color and measure 5 x 7 inches, though there are other sizes as well. In some cases, the negatives are also included. The photographs concentrate on new construction and areas slated for development and were often used to establish insurance policies and settle claims. Legard stored them in three-ring binders arranged by job. This arrangement has been preserved, and there is no item level indexing available. The folder titles are taken from the names Legard assigned each job.
Arrangement
Box: folder
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
AncestryLibrary.com. 1940 United States Census. www.ancestrylibrary.com (accessed 10 May 2013).
Loudoun Times-Mirror. "S. Campbell Legard, Well-Known Farmer." 3 December 1981.
Location of Originals
This collection is stored off-site. Advance notice is required to retrieve records. Please contact reference staff to make arrangements.
Other Finding Aid
Past Perfect catalogue records
Related Material
None
Separated Material
None
Contents List
- (Box 1)
  - Loudoun County Government Center Groundbreaking Ceremony, Leesburg, 1995
  - Leesburg and Luck Stone Quarry, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Ball's Bluff, Big Springs, Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg from ground, 1994
  - Toll Road Leesburg, 1994
  - Leesburg, 1994
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Evergreen Rd. High School Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Airport, Leesburg, 2001
  - New High School and Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Rt. 7 and Leesburg, 2001
  - Ball's Bluff and Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Near Dulles Toll Road and Near Mary Ford's Bridge, Leesburg, 2001
- (Box 2)
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997
- (Box 3)
  - Unidentified, n.d.
  - Unidentified, 1993
  - Carol Laycock, Hamilton, 1999
  - Jeff Fraker Home, Tom DuRant Home, Mullholland Home, 704 Homes on Canby Lane, Hamilton, n.d.
  - Purcellville and Hamilton, 2003
  - Near Rt. 9, 1 mile east of E. Peacock Farm, Wheatland, n.d.
  - Unidentified, n.d.
  - Loudoun Orchard Rd. area, 2003
  - Madican Rt. 9, 2002, 2004
  - Spotts Rt. 9, 2004
  - 1 mile NE of Rt. 9 and 287, Wheatland, n.d.
  - Bill and Sally Oblas, 2001
  - Beacon Hill, Drum Heller, Plane Crash, 2004
  - Hamilton, 1996, 2004, 2006, 2008
  - Rt. 9 and 704 area Hamilton, n.d.
  - Lansdowne Area, 1997
  - Ashburn, n.d.
  - Whites Ferry Rd. Leesburg, 1997
  - Spring Wood, n.d.
  - Franklin Park (Personal Note "Sally Keifer" enclosed), 1997
  - 4-H Fair, 1997
  - Next to Beacon Hill at Rt. 7, Next to Clark's Gap, 1996
  - Sam Welch 704 Farm, 1996
  - C. Stowers Waterford, 1996
  - Bazaco, R. J. Legard, 1996
  - Broadview, 1996
  - Ebenezer Church, Neersville; Mt. Olivet, Lovettsville; Rehobeth Church, Lovettsville, n.d.
  - George Fitzwater, 1996
  - Sim Cotton, 1996
  - Beacon Hill, 1996
  - Short Hill, Mt. Hillsboro, 1996
  - Birch Hollow, Hillsboro, 1996
  - Morven Park, Leesburg, 1996
  - Mt. Fire, Rt. 601 (N), near Tower, 1996
  - Bill Oblas, Roland Adamison, 1996
  - Rt. 9 and 690 Hillsboro; Herb Pearson Farm, Leesburg; Water tower, 1996
  - Catoctin Circle, Leesburg, n.d.
  - 4-H, 1996
  - Catoctin Stud., Waterford, 2000
  - Firestone, Catoctin Stud., 2000
  - Photographs by Pam Hoovey. Middleburg area, Rowley, Carter, Aldie Mills, next to Little Oatlands at 15 S Church, 1996
  - Ed Mongomery farm, Hillsboro, 1996
  - Ayrshire Farm, 2000
  - Loudoun Hospital Benefit, 2000
- (Box 4)
  - (WAS) C.Y. Halls Farm, Hamilton, 2002
  - Layton's, 1997
  - Larry Johnston, Hillsboro, 1999
  - Dr. Joe and Donna Rogers, 2004
  - Lovettsville, 1994
  - Lovettsville; Brunswick, also Potomac River; East, MD; Georges Mill, Lovettsvill; Rt 287 Lovettsville, 2003
  - George's Mill, Lovettsville, 2004
  - Loudoun Hospital Center Dedication (Pamphlet), 1997
  - Hospital, Lansdowne, 2002, 2003
  - Hospital, Hughes Center, Lansdowne, 2004
  - Lucketts, 1992, 2004
- (Box 5)
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Hospital, Leesburg, 2001
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Auto accident at Davis Ave. and S King St., Leesburg, 2000
  - Ashburn Ruritan meeting at ANMC, 2000
  - Raspberry Falls, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Toll Brothers, Leesburg, 2000
  - Methodist Church, Rt. 621, Evergreen Rd., Leesburg, 2000
  - Hospital, Lansdowne, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Air photos, 1988
  - Leesburg, 2004
- (Box 6)
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1999
- (Box 7)
  - Round Hill, 1992
  - Rod Huebers, Round Hill, 2002
  - Round Hill, 2008
  - Round Hill, Stoneleigh Golf, 2000
  - New John Deere, 2003; Dr. Towes area, Round Hill looking S, 2006
  - Round Hill, 2000
  - Hot air ballons, Round Hill, 2001
  - Round Hill, 1996
  - Round Hill, 2001
  - Purcellville, 2004
  - Round Hill n.d.
  - Unidentified, 2004
  - Purcellville; Carver School; Brown Farm; Pott's Dogwood Farm, 2006
  - H. Ralph Field's, Purcellville, 2000
  - Purcellville, Home School Building, 1991
  - Unidentified, 1991
  - Dick Wrights Farm, Purcellville, 2000
  - Franklin Park, Purcellville, 2000, 2003, 2006
  - Purcellville, 2003
  - On old Hillen Dale Farm, C Wilson Farm, 2003
  - 4-H, 1992
  - 4-H Fair Grounds, 2004
  - 4-H, 2005
  - Unidentified, n.d.
  - Inova Loudoun Hospital, Leesburg, with CD, 2006
  - Inova Loudoun Hospital, Lansdowne area with CD, 2008
  - Leesburg, Lansdowne, 2008
  - Lansdowne Hospital area, 2008
  - Morven Park, 2008
  - Unidentified miscellaneous, 1990, 1991, 1992, 1997
  - Deb Welsh, Evergreen Rd., Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg; Ben and Ruth Epperson; Paris, 2000
  - 4-H Grounds, Leesburg, 2000
  - Shenstone, Leesburg, 2000
  - Unidentified, 2000
  - Land Fill, 2000
  - Bud Greenfield Farm, N on 15 from Leesburg, 2002
  - Bud Greenfield, N on Rt 15 from Leesburg, at Lime Stone Creek, 2000
  - Thrifty Car Rental, Leesburg, 2000
  - Miscellaneous, 1996,1997
- (Box 8)
  - Leesburg; Purcellville, about 1995; Greenway, 1995; New golf course Ross old landing strip, 1995; horse races, n.d.
  - Leesburg, 1995
  - Leesburg; River Creek, 1996
  - Leesburg, Potomac Station, 1996; Leesburg, taken by Pam Hovey, Sam Legard, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Beacon Hill, Shenstone, 2001, 2002
- (Box 9)
  - Crosstrails, next to airport, Leesburg; School in Round Hill; Landfill south of Leesburg; Saratoga, Legacy, Rt. 9 W of Hillsboro, 2006
  - Hospital area, Leesburg, 2006
  - Saratoga Project, Legacy Homes, Hillsboro; Bob Legard, Morrisonville, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - N Waterford, Leesburg, 2006
  - Leesburg, Lansdowne area; Hospital, Lansdowne area, 2006
  - Lansdowne area, 2003
  - Hamilton Fire Station; Round Hill; Purcellville, 2004
  - Purcellville; Round Hill, 2004
  - Loudoun Orchard's area 704; Round Hill, 2005
  - Karen Cooper, Round Hill, 2005
  - Unidentified large photos (Leesburg housing development), 2004
- (Box 10)
  - Unidentified hospital, ferry, 1980-1990
  - Schools on N end of Leesburg, 2004
  - Greenway, airport area, Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg airport, hospital, Lansdowne schools, Leesburg, 2004
  - Costco, Kohls, Leesburg, 2004
  - Lansdowne, 2004
  - Hospital, Lansdowne area, 2004
  - Hughs Center, Lansdowne area, 2004
  - Leesburg, 2004
  - Across from Rolling Acres, Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg, 2003
  - Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg, 2004
- (Box 11)
  - Leesburg, 1988
  - Leesburg, 1988
  - Leesburg, 1988
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg and Morven Park Dog Show, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg and Potomac River, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
- (Box 12)
  - Goose Creek fire; Allen Studio, Middleburg; Jim Wakeham; Leesburg; Unidentified from Allen Studio; Contact Sheets, 1976-1979
  - Leesburg area (black and white contact prints), 1962; unidentified 1976, 1977 and n.d
  - Unidentified, n.d.; Unidentified, 1964; Leesburg, 1982 and 1985; Contact Sheets
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - Lansdowne hospital, 2006
  - Berryville; Leesburg, Lovetteville; Purcellville, 2006
  - Berryville; Leesburg; Purcellville, 2006
  - Purcellville, Leesburg, and Round Hill, 2006
  - Leesburg, Purcellville, Berryville, Lucketts, Lovettsville, 2006
  - Hamilton, Neersville, Hillsborough, and Purcellville, CD and negatives, 2008
  - Purcellville, Berryville, and Hamilton, 2008
- (Box 13)
  - Leesburg, 2004
  - Leesburg, 1994, 1995, 2001, and 2004
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - Leesburg, 1992, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2003 and 2004
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - Leesburg, 1996
  - Leesburg, 1996
- (Box 14)
  - Round Hill, Wheatland Farm, 2004
  - Safety Center, Hamilton, Purcellville, Round Hill, 2004
  - 2.5 miles W of Round Hill, on N side of Rt. 7, 2003
  - Round Hill, 2005
  - Round Hill, 1997
  - Round Hill, 1989
  - Round Hill, 2004
  - Round Hill, 2003
  - Round Hill, 2002
  - Round Hill, 2000
  - S on Rt. 719, Round Hill, area, 1999
  - New subdivision .5 mile W of Round Hill on N side of Rt. 7, Round Hill, 1995
  - Round Hill, 2006
  - Round Hill, 2004
  - Wood Grove and Round Hill, 2004
  - Round Hill, 2003
  - Purcellville, 2001
  - Bill and Joyce Hibbles, Purcellville, 2001
  - School near Hamilton and Purcellville, 2001
  - Purcellville, 2001
  - Field's Farm, Purcellville, 2006
- (Box 16)
  - Hospital Awards, 2002
  - Loudoun Hospital Awards Program, 2002
  - Loudoun Hospital (Hearing), 2002
  - Loudoun Hospital, 2002
  - Loudoun Hospital area, 2002
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 2002
  - Loudoun Hospital Awards, 2002
  - Motorola Air, 1996
  - Motorola Air, 1996
  - Cornwall Pavilion, Lutheran Church, Leesburg, 2007
  - Leesburg, 2007
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Leesburg, 2002
  - Dry Mill Rd. and Leesburg, 2002
- (Box 17)
  - Leesburg, Contact Sheets and Proofs from Allen Studio and Camera Shop, Middleburg, 1959-1960
  - Photo by Stanley Wortman, Sam Legard, pilot, Contact Sheets, 1964
  - Contact Sheets, Unidentified, 1965 and 1969; West Boxwell, 1968
  - Contact Sheets, 1971, 1972, 1973, 1974 and 1975
  - Middleburg, Berryville, Hillsboro, Purcellville, 2008
  - Berryville, Purcellville, Leesburg, Middleburg, and Lucketts, 2008
  - Philomont, 2002 and 2006; Linda Lawson (?) 1999; Rita Walstast, Editor, Loudoun Book, 2002
  - Bill and Polly Harrison; Hamilton, 1999
  - Leesburg, 1984, 1987, 1989, 1988, 2004 and 2008
  - Clarks Gap, 1999; Goose Creek, 2002; 2000 Town of Leesburg Water Quality Report; Karen Title Co., Leesburg, 1999; Reese Clarks Gap, Leesburg, 2000; Lansdowne, 2004
  - Purcellville, 1984, 1999, 2002, 2003 and 2006
  - Round Hill, 1995, 1998, and 1999; Fox Farm, Round Hill, 1999; Dr. Towe 1999
  - Franklin Park; Round Hill, 2000 and 2005
- (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, 1999 and 2000; Dr. Olsers (Clarks Gap?), 1998; Sam Brown Farm, 2000; Bobby Brown Farm, 1998
  - Wheatland, 1998; Mt. Gilead (Dr. Oliver), 2001; Hamilton, 2004
  - Leesburg, Purcellville, Hamilton, Round Hill, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - Leesburg, 2002 and 2003
  - Leesburg, 2003
  - Leesburg, 2003
  - Leesburg; Kohl's, Target, Costco, 2004
  - Hospital and Lansdowne; Leesburg, April, 2004
- (Box 19)
  - Purcellville, 2006
  - Purcellville, 2005
  - Round Hill, Hamilton, Purcellville, 2005
  - Robert Pitts, Karen Cooper, Purcellville, 2002
  - Purcellville, 2002
  - Purcellville, 2003
  - Negatives of Purcellville, Negatives of Leesburg, Negatives of Hamilton, 2003
  - Franklin Park and Purcellville, 2003
  - Water Treatment Plant, Purcellville, 2000
  - Purcellville, 2000
  - Leesburg, and Greenway Toll Road, 1995
- (Box 20)
  - Ferry, Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Leesburg Airport, Leesburg, 1993
  - Leesburg, 1997
  - Walmart, Leesburg, 1993
  - Food Lion, Leesburg, 1993
  - Leesburg, 1993
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1990
- (Box 21)
  - Goose Creek, East; Lansdowne, 2001
  - Dog Show, Morven Park, 1999
  - Lansdowne, 1999
  - Dutch Co., Ashburn, 1999
  - River Creek, Leesburg 1999
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 1999
  - Lansdowne Area, 1999
  - Lansdowne Area, 2006
  - River Creek, Leesburg, 2005
  - Lansdowne Hospital, GW, BioTech, NTSB, 2003
  - Lansdowne Hospital and Lansdowne Area, 2003
  - Lansdowne Area, 2002
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 1997
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 1997
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 1997
  - Lansdowne Hospital, 1997
  - Lansdowne Hospital Area, 2000
  - River Creek, 2000
  - Lansdowne Hospital Area, 2007
  - Lansdowne Hospital Area, 2007
  - Hospital, Lansdowne, 2002
  - Lansdowne Area, 2000
  - Loudoun Hospital Area, 2002
- (Box 22)
  - Cumberland, MD Airport; Richard Bechtold, Sam Legard; Berryville, 2007
  - Winchester, 2007
  - Purcellville, 2007
  - Berryville, 2007
  - Berryville, Winchester, Purcellville, Leesburg, (Goose Creek Area), 2007
  - Richard Bechtold, Martinsburg; Dr. Timberlake's New Office and Winchester and Winchester Airport, 2007
  - Leesburg, 2007
  - Berryville, 2007
  - Inova, Loudoun County, 2007
  - Unknown
  - Local Farms: Wheatland; Harrison (Bill & Polly); Hutchinson (Larry & Betty); Miller (Bill & Carol), Rogers, Howard; Pearson (Herb & Shirley); Turner, Woody; Layton, Tom; Ballard, Kent; Bazaco, Dr; Waterford, Hillsboro, n.d.
  - Local Farms: Webb, B.J.; Manning; Compher; 4H Grounds; Shotwell, Spotts, n.d.
  - Purcellville, n.d.
  - Leesburg, Thrifty Auto Rental, 2000
  - 4-H (Loudoun County ), 1998
  - Raspberry Falls, 1998
  - River Creek, 1998
  - Leisure World, 1998
  - Leesburg Christian School (Fire), 1998
  - Shenstone, Leesburg, 2000
- (Box 23)
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - Purcellville, 2006
  - East of Goose Creek; Lansdowne, 2003
  - Woodburn Estates, 2004
  - Mark Caldwell, Fred Minter, Dan Spotts, 2004
  - Round Hill, Purcellville, Hamilton, 2004
  - Near Wheatland, 2004
  - Grace Keenan, Roger Zurn and Beacon Hill, Waterford, 2004
  - Hillsboro, 1995, 1998, 2002-2004
  - Hillsboro Area, n.d.
  - Hillsboro Area, n.d.
  - S C Legard Farm, Hillsboro, 1998, 2000
  - Short Hill, 1999
  - Bill Kren's Airfield (Rt 9), 2000
  - Wayne Hardy Farm, 2002
  - Hillsboro Area, n.d.
  - Hamilton Ruritan (Flyers, Members List, Photos of H and W), n.d.
  - Leesburg, 2007
  - Purcellville, 2007
  - Middleburg, 2007
  - Berryville, 2007
  - Clark County, Stevens City, 2007
- (Box 24)
  - County Government Center, Leesburg, 1995
  - Leesburg, 1995
  - Raspberry Falls Gold Course, Morven Park, Leesburg, 1995
  - South end of Airport, Leesburg, 1995
  - Purcellville, 1991
  - Leesburg, 1991
- (Box 25)
  - Purcellville, 1998
  - Point of Rocks, MD; Lucketts; Raspberry Falls Golf Course, 2005
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - 4-H Grounds, Leesburg, 2005
  - Hamilton Ruritan Club, Leesburg, 2005
  - Leesburg, 2005
  - Across from Beacon Hill, Leesburg, 2000
  - Beacon Hill, 2000
  - Beacon Hill, 1999
  - Beacon Hill, Leesburg, 2000
  - Beacon Hill, 2000
  - Leesburg, 1990
  - Tom Donohoe, Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1990
  - Leesburg, 2003
  - Beacon Hill, 2000
  - Purcellville, 1989
  - Franklin Park, Purcellville, 1998
  - Purcellville, 2005
  - Purcellville, 2006
  - Cockerill Farm, Purcellville, 2005
  - Purcellville, 2007
- (Box 26)
  - Purcellville, 1996
  - Purcellville, 1996
  - Purcellville, 1996-1997
  - Purcellville, 1997
  - Purcellville, 1997
  - Purcellville, 2001
  - Purcellville, 2003
  - Purcellville, 2003
  - Purcellville, 2003
  - Leesburg, 2005, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2005, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2006
  - Leesburg, 2006
- (Box 27)
  - 4-H Front Royal, 2003
  - 4-H Fair (Contact sheet from Shenandoah Photographics, Inc. also includes photo with two men), 2003
  - 4-H Fairgrounds and Fair, August 1999
  - 4-H Fairgrounds, 2000
  - 4-H Fairgrounds, 2003
  - 70th birthday party for Frank Keesling, October 20, 2001
  - 4-H Fair, 2002
  - "Jackson Kiss a Pig!" at the Loudoun County 4-H Fair, 2001
  - 4-H, 2002
  - 4-H, 1999
  - 4-H Grounds, 1993
  - 4-H Grounds, 1965, 1974, 1980
  - Unidentified miscellaneous, n.d.
  - Leesburg North on 15 near Limestone Creek, 1988
  - Bill and Polly Harrison, Mt. Gilead, 1997
  - Loudoun Landfill, 1997
  - Lansdowne, 1995
  - Leesburg, 1995
  - Unidentified, 1988, 1990
  - Leesburg United Methodist Church handouts, 1988
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Unidentified, 1989
  - Frostburg, MD airport, F Lakes, Leesburg, 1989
  - Allan and Nancy (Legard Morggie's?) Negatives. Morggies dress for Karen's wedding, August 20, 1989
  - Lot under development, Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Leesburg, 1989
  - Unidentified, 1989
  - Lovettsville, 2001
  - Unidentified, 2008
  - Lovettsville, 2008
  - Householder, R.D. David Douglason, Costco Mgr., Lovettsville, 2004
  - Lovettsville, 2000
  - George's Mill, 2000
  - Hickman Farm, Lovettsville, 1996
  - Lovettsville, 1996
  - Stock's Farm, Lovettsville, 1999
  - Round Hill, Rt. 719 North, 2001
  - Round Hill, 1999
- (Box 28)
  - Leesburg, 1991
  - Country Club, Leesburg, 1990
  - White's Ferry, Leesburg Hospital, Leesburg, 1990
  - Woodlea Manor, Leesburg, 1990
  - Leesburg, 1990
  - Leesburg, 1990
  - Leesburg, 1988
  - Woodlea Manor, Leesburg, 1988
  - Leesburg, 1988
- (Box 29)
  - Miller Drive, Leesburg, 1993
  - Purcellville, 2004
  - Purcellville, 2004
  - Berryville, 2007
  - Leesburg, 2007
  - Route 9 and Old Waterford Rd., 2007
  - 4-H Grounds, Leesburg, 2007
  - Leesburg, 2007
  - Ralph Fields Jr. Farm, Purcellville, 2000
  - Purcellville, 2000
  - Purcellville, 2000
  - Purcellville, 1999
  - Purcellville, 1999
- (Box 31)
  - Raspberry Falls Golf Course, 1995, 1996
  - Raspberry Falls Golf Course, 1996
  - Raspberry Falls Golf Course, 1996
  - Purcellville, Round Hill, Franklin Park, 1995, 1999, 2002, 2005
  - Round Hill, Bill Kelley Farm, 1989, 1995, 2000, 2002
  - White's Ferry, 1996
  - Unidentified, 1996
  - Unidentified, 1996
  - Goose Creek, 1996
  - Old Ashburn school, 1996
  - Unidentified, 1996
  - Oatlands, 1996
  - Bill and Polly Harrison, 1996
  - Lowe's Island, 1996
  - River Creek, 1996
  - Unidentified, 1996. Black and white image from 1962
  - Purcellville, (photos and CD), 2008
- (Box 32)
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 2000
  - Leesburg, 1995
  - Leesburg, 2001
  - Lansdowne and Inova Loudoun Hospital, 1995
  - Leesburg, St. John's Church, and Woodlea, 1995
  - Leesburg and Morven Park, 1995
  - Greenway, 1995
  - Leesburg (includes car and airplane accidents), 1993
- (Box 33)
  - Franklin Park and Purcellville, 1998-1999
  - Franklin Park and Purcellville, 2000-2002
  - Purcellville, 2003-2004
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1992
  - Leesburg and Lipscomb Farm, 1992
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1998
  - Leesburg, 1999
- (Box 34)
  - Beacon Hill, 1999
  - Church, 1988
  - Waterford, 1999
  - Paeonian Springs, 1999
  - Godfrey, 1999
  - Unknown, 1999
  - Waterford Fair, 1999
  - Waterford, 1993
  - Waterford, 1998
  - Lovettsville, Milltown Stocks Farm, 1999
  - Animal Shelter on Rt. 9, 1999
  - Firestone, Waterford, 1999
  - Hamilton, 1997, 1999, 2002, 2006
  - Lovettsville, Morrisonville, 1997
  - Leesburg, 1969, 1979, 1958, 1987, 1992
  - Round Hill Villages, 2001
  - Safety Center, Hamilton, 2004
  - Route 7 Bypass between Hamilton and Purcellville, 1999
  - Hamilton, 2001
  - School Site between Hamilton and Purcellville, 2001
  - Beacon Hill, Hamilton, 2001
  - Sam Brown's Farm and Hamilton, 2002
  - Hamilton, 2002
  - Hamilton, 1989-1990
  - Hamilton, 2002
  - Hamilton, 2003
  - Hamilton, 2004
  - Hamilton, 2004